(忆往昔)
Ed和Harry
Ed and Harry.
打鬼特工队
The Ghostfacers.
你们在这儿干什么
What the hell are you doing here.
我们就属于这里
We belong here.
我们是专业人士
We're professionals.
什么专业
Professional what.
超自然现象调查员
Paranormal investigators.
这里的那东西
This stuff right here,this.
能领我们走向辉煌
Is our ticket to the big time.
名利 金钱
Fame,money.
性欲
Sex.
大把的美妞
With girls.
我们是一家人
We are family.
我们之间
Everything.
发生的一切
That has ever gone wrong between us.
都是因为 我们是一家人
Has been because we're family.
怎么了 我们现在就不是了吗
So what?We're not family now.
我的意思是 你想干活的话
I'm saying you wanna work.
我们可以一起
Let's work.
你是说你想让所有事都
You said you wanted to keep things.
- 公事化 - 我想让我们之间的事
- Strictly business - I wanna keep things.
从此以后 公事化
Strictly business between us.
你那天说的话
About what you said the other day.
我以为你没意见
I thought that wouldn't bother you.
我想事情可能没有那么周全
I may not think things all the way through.
但是我做的一切
But what I do.
都是因为它们是正确的事
I do because it's the right thing.
你并不是为了我才救我
You didn't save me,for me.
你是为了你自己
You did it, for you
(如今)
(斯普林代尔 华盛顿州)
妈
Mom.
妈 你回来了吗
Mom,are you home.
911 请问您有什么紧急情况
911,what is your emergency.
有人在我的房间里
There's someone in my room.
请问您住在哪儿
What is your location.
您能给我们提供一个地址吗 女士
Can you give us a location,ma'am.
您还在吗
Are you still there.
女士
Ma'am.
请不要挂断电话
Please do not hang up.
我正在追踪您的电话来源
I've begun tracing your call.
但是我需要您保持通话
But I need you to stay on the line for me.
我出去一趟
All right,I'll be back.
你 你去哪儿
You...Where're you heading.
华盛顿州 发现一个案子
Washington,I caught a case.
你不想让我跟去吗
You want me to come with.
你会去吗
You wanna come.
去查案子吗 为什么不会
On a hunt?Why wouldn't I.
我也说不好 因为最近你总是
I don't know,man.'Cause lately with you.
阴晴不定的
Up is down and down is...sideways,you know.
我怎么知道你想干什么
I don't know what you want.
好吧 你想来就来吧
Okay,you want in,fine.
没问题
Sure thing.
这是从案发现场泄露的照片
Photo leaked from crime scene.
一个女孩被杀死在房间里
Girl was murdered in a room.
门窗都从里面反锁了
Door was locked.Windows were locked.
后面那个疤脸是谁
Who was the wallflower.
问得好
Exactly.
目前来看 应该是个鬼魂
Best guess.Ghost caught on the film.
所以 你是要跟来吗
So you're coming.
我像是要留在这里的样子吗
Does it look like I'm staying
(斯普林代尔 华盛顿州)
我擦了好几个小时
I scrubbed for hours.
整条地毯都浸透了
I'll have to rip up the carpet.
我女儿 Cassy
My daughter,Cassy.
她自己挑的颜色
She picked up the color herself.
请您 节哀顺变 Smiles太太
We're...very sorry for your loss,Mrs.Miles.
您之前说 Cassy没有 敌人
You mentioned Cassy had no known enemies.
那在家里有没有
What about...at home.
什么异常的现象
Anything...unusual you may have noticed.
比如电流异常 或者灯
Like electricity acting out or lights.
闪烁不定 电视信号时有时无
Flickering?TV on the fritz.
不 家里电视信号很好
No,no fritzing.
也没有气温骤降区域
No cold spots either.
不好意思 我就是好奇
Sorry,out of curiosity.
您为什么要提气温骤降
Why do you mention cold spots.
很抱歉 听起来可能很奇怪 但是
I'm sorry that might sounds strange,but.
已经过去3天了
It's been 3 days since.
警察什么也没查到
The police have found nothing.
我就 我就卖了房子
I'd have...I'd have to sell my house.
雇了一个私人调查员
To afford a private investigator.
所以当超自然现象专家致电给我的时候
So when the supernaturalists called.
不好意思
Sorry,the.
您是说超自然现象专家吗
Supernaturalists.
我知道FBI肯定不相信这种怪事
I know to the FBI is not exactly orthodox.
但是这些人知道很多
But these men had answers that.
别人不知道的事 我
No one else had and I.
我欠Cassy的
I owe it,to Cassy.
都怪我没听她的话
To listen.
他们既然提起了气温骤降点
You know,they brought up cold spots.
是跟什么有关
In relation to.
我猜是什么超自然征兆吧
Signs of the paranormal,I suppose.
他们今天会过来看看
They are coming by today to take a look.
请问这些
Ma'am,did these.
超自然学专家有没有告诉你他们的名字
Supernaturalists give you a name.
狗娘养的混蛋
Son of a bitch.
猜我发现了什么
Oh,whoa,look we got.
又多了两个粉丝
Two more followers.
Harry 是我们在图书馆做采访的那两个
Harry,it's from the library interview we did.
不错
Nice.
喂
Hey,whoa.
Dana又发什么了
What did Dana post.
不是 就是她换了她资料里的照片
No,it's just she changed her profile pic.
明显能看出来 是被裁过的
And it's cropped but you can clearly see.
肩膀还被一个男的搂着
A guy's arm around her.
她笑的花枝乱颤 跟小妖精似的
And she's smiling like the dickens.
呃 可能 是柏拉图式的
Yeah,it...it could be a platonic.
我是说那个搂着的手
Arm that's touching her.
Winchester兄弟 真棒
The Winchesters,yeah.
- 不可能会有人 - 这么想
- Says nobody - Ever.
闭上嘴听我说事情
All right,shut up and listen.
接下来是这样发展的
This is how it's gonna go.
你们两个丢人现眼的 立刻回你们
You two clowns are gonna get into.
停在外面的神秘机器里去
That mystery machine outside and.
然后离开这里
Are gonna leave the town.
不然我会在你们膝盖上开两个洞
Or I'm gonna put holes in your knees.
请问你们要点什么
Can I get you guys anything.
有没有什么
Something.
我们准备好买单了
We're ready for the bill.
这盘子没洗干净
There are still crud on this plate.
去水槽那里重新洗一遍
Hit the sink and do it right.
对不起 Trey
Sorry,Trey.
首先
First of all.
你们吓不倒我们
You guys don't scare us.
完全吓不倒
Not at all.
来和我的小手枪问个好
Say hola to my little pistola.
我是应该被你的腹毛吓到
Am I supposed to be impressed by that treasure trail.
还是被你塞在裤子里的女士小手枪吓到
Or the lady gun you got hide in your pants there.
都有
Both.
不管你们喜不喜欢
Look,whether you like it or not.
我们已经控制好局势了
We're handling this situation.
是吗
Really.
我只看见两个为了虚荣不择手段的人
'Casue I see a couple of fame whores.
把目标对准了一个刚失去孩子的母亲
Who are pointing their camera on a mom who just lost her kid.
我们是调查员
We are investigators.
- 我们有权 - 不
- We have every right - No.
你们没有
No,you don't.
知道为什么吗 因为你们
You want to why?'Cause you're just.
只会给我们添麻烦
Gonna get in our way.
或者让更多的人被害
Or you're gonna get somebody else killed.
对 所以
That's right,so.
你们要么走出去
You can either walk out of here.
要么爬出去
Or crawl.
自己决定
Up to you.
我的天 放松点儿好吗
Oh my god manudo,will you guys relax.
我们知道我们在干什么
We know what we're doing.
- 对 - 是吗
- Yup - Really.
那你们队里其他人都去哪儿了
Then what about the rest of the Bad News Bears.
我记得 我记得有个胖子
Where's the...where's the fat one.
还有个女孩儿 是还有个女孩儿对吧
And the girl,there's a girl,right.
他们背 我们放弃了他们
They...we dropped them.
他们 拖了我们后腿
They're...they were dead-weight.
他们都还活着
Well,they are still alive.
绝对都还活着
They are...they're totally alive.
知道了 那么
I see,so.
掺和这事儿的就只有你们两个蠢蛋
That's just...the dumpy duo then.
那太好了 事实是这样的
Well,that's great.So here's the deal.
一个鬼能5秒内放倒你们两个人
A ghost,will land you two dead in 5 seconds flat.
鬼吗
A ghost.
他们以为是鬼
Oh,they think it's a ghost.
根本不是鬼
It's so not a ghost.
好吧
Okay,we'll bite.
你们觉得是什么
What do you think it is.
我 能让我来吗
Can I...Can I do it this time.
- 你来 - 好
- You got it - Okay.
我已经等这一刻很久了
I've waited all my life for this.
就不告诉你们 贱人
Amazon me,bitches.
我真的会 一枪崩了你
I will,shoot you.
贱人
Bitches.
我们刚说了
Like we're saying.
你们是要走吧 对吧 太好了
You're just going.Right?Great.
聊得真愉快
Good talk.
这俩人真是 营养过剩
Fifty shades of...way too much protein.
Dean
Dean.
怎么了
Yeah.
Ed和Harry写了本书
Ed and Harry wrote a book.
- 什么 - 嗯
- What - Yeah.
末影人大揭秘
The Skinny on Thinman.
美国著名超自然学专家著
By America's foremost supernaturalists.
末影人是什么鬼东西
What the hell is a Thinman.
不知道
I don't know.
看
Check that out though.
貌似还真像
That...does kinda look like.
Cassy Smiles背后的那个东西
Whatever was behind Cassy Miles,right.
你怎么不说像Garth 脸被削掉的版本
Or Garth if somebody shaved his face off.
- 真可怕 - 这儿
- Big Whoop - Here we go.
末影人 最初源于某网站的都市传说
Thinman,an urban legend started on a world wide web.
他们潜伏在被害人的背影里
Lurks in the background of his victims' lives.
准备好后就杀死被害人
Until he's ready to kill them.
说得对 因为
Yeah,because.
所有从网上传出来的东西都是真的
Everything started on the Internet is...true.
比如 一条鲨鱼攻击了一架直升机
Like...a shark attacking the helicopter.
他们是不是也写了本书
They write a book on that one too.
老兄 不管是否真实 成千上万的人
Dude,real or not,thousands of people have.
都在这个网上留过言 就好像末影人是
Posted this site.It's like this Thinman is like.
大脚怪一样的存在
The new bigfoot or something.
或者末影人只是鬼的新名字
Or Thinman is just a ghost with a brand name.
你这么说是因为你觉得
You saying that cause you really think.
那就是鬼 还是因为
It's a ghost or because you.
你不喜欢打鬼特工队
Don't like the Ghostfacers.
别忘了EMF在Cassy房间里的度数有多惊人
Don't forget we hit EMF in Cassy's room.
是 但是那房子旁边挨着电缆线
Right,but the house was next door to power lines.
有可能影响读数
Which can effect read.
一个女孩儿死在封闭的房间里 Sam
A girl died in a locked room,Sam.
明显就是鬼干的啊
Spells ghost right there.
也可能是没锁之前溜进去的
Maybe it got in there before it was locked up.
谁知道呢 Dean 但是全世界的人
Who knows,Dean.But how could people all over.
都看到同一个鬼
The world see the same ghost.
鬼不能到处乱跑吧
Spirits don't exactly hop around.
我知道
I know that.
但是现在 阴阳交界处出问题了
But right now the veil's all kinds of screwed,okay.
鬼爱怎么跑就怎么跑
A ghost can popping up anywhere.
是 但是末影人几年前就出现了
Yeah,Dean.But Thinman sightings date back a couple of years.
交界是什么时候出问题的来着
The veil's only been a problem for like what.
6个月前而已
The last six month.
现在还有人坚持自己看见了猫王Elvis呢
You know,people still see Elvis all over the damn place.
我的意思是 两个蠢货
Look,all I'm saying is douchewheels.
才不什么专家
Ain't expert on crap.
你在干什么
What are you doing.
我在查本地讣告通知
I'm checking the local deaths.
看有没有人有可能变成闹事的鬼魂
See if there's any candidates for ghosts.
衣柜
The closet.
Cassy的生命之光随日落而灭
The setting of the sunset of Cassy's life.
- Harry - 怎么了
- Harry - Yeah.
你能不能别在facebook上
Come on,man,would you please stop facebook.
视奸你前女友主页了吗
Stalking your ex-girlfriend.
我就知道
I was right.
她把自己的感情状态
She changed her relationshop status to.
改成了 复杂
It's complicated.
这个词到底是什么意思
What does that even mean.
谁管什么意思 你跟她已经分手了
Who cares?You broke up with her.
跟这姑娘有关的所有事情都很复杂
Everything about that girl is complicated.
我是说 她给自己买奶油泡芙
Okay,I mean she gets a cream puff.
让你吃里面的奶油
She tells you to take the filling.
只是她的怪癖而已
It's just puffs.
是啊 真的挺怪异的
Yeah,that was some pretty messed up stuff.
好吧 我很抱歉
Okay,uh-I'm-I'm sorry.
好吧 我很好
Okay I'm good,back on game.
我们离末影人又近了一步 Ed
So close to finding Thinman,Ed.
我能闻到它们
I can smell them.
闻到它们特有的体味
I can smell its musk.
比以往更近一步
Close than ever.
现在的情况很严峻 Harry
This is really serious,Harry.
是啊
Yeah.
Winchester兄弟都一路查到这儿了
I mean the Winchesters are here and.
我可不想被Sam和Dean打断膝盖
I don't want my knees blown off by Sam and Dean.
但你有没有想过 我们是不是应该
Have you ever thought that we might just,you know.
放弃这个案子
Bail on this.
什么
What.
你到底 到底出什么毛病了
What the-what the hell is wrong with you.
决不能让那两个拖油瓶抢了我们的功劳
We can't let those jockstraps steal our glory.
别管他们怎么想的
Don't care what they think.
他们连twitter都没有
They don't even have a twitter.
我们能找到末影人的 Ed
We're gonna find Thinman,Ed.
为了我们的家庭
For our families.
为了Dana
For Dana.
而且 还能让你前女友大跌眼镜
Oh,so,it's about your ex eating her words.
让所有不相信我们的人 都见鬼去吧
It's about making all the haters eat their words.
Maggie还有Spruce 背叛我们的人
Maggie and Spruce,the deserters.
他们想过他们的正常生活
They wanna lead a normal life.
照我说 那算什么东西
I mean,what is that.
- 见鬼去吧 - 见鬼去吧
- Screw them - Screw them.
等我们找到末影人
When we find Thinman.
他们会成为我们的Phill医生吗
Are they gonna be our Dr.Phill.
不
No.
我们会变成自己的Phill医生
We're gonna be our Dr.Phill.
没错
Oh yeah.
- 拿好你的摄像机 - 没问题
- Press your record - You got it.
等我指示
Wait for it.
- 好了吗 - 好了
- Ready - Yeah.
一个处于青春期少女的卧室
The bedroom of a teenage girls is.
意味着两样东西
Meant for two things.
欢声与笑语
Giggles and joy.
直到有一天晚上
Until one night.
末影人把这一切变成了鲜血
Thinman turned the giggles into blood.
你酷炫极了
You're so money right now.
- 你喜欢 - 演的很好
- You like that? - This is good stuff.
女孩子们肯定会喜欢我们的作品
I just gonna pay off in ladies,Ed.
蜂拥而至的女孩子
Lots of ladies.
到时候我们 我们需要潜水面具
We're gonna need,we're gonna need snorkels.
因为我们会在钞票泳池里游
Cause we're gonna be swimming around in so much.
我觉得你们可能会 口渴
Thought you boys might be...thirsty.
谢谢 看上去味道很不错
Please,that sounds delicious.
好吧
Okay.
这6个月里
All right,over the passed six months.
一共有3起非正常死亡案件
There've been three unatural deaths in Springdale.
没有能和Cassy Miles有关系的
None of them connected to Cassy Miles.
也没有能跟暴力事件扯上边的
None of them is violent.
听起来很像是
Okay,that is not exactly.
复仇鬼魂
A recipe for revengefull spirit.
我查到有很多与末影人有关的
There have been a bunch of unexplained death.
未解死亡案件
Pinned on Thinman.
受害人死后几周
A vit dies,then a couple of weeks later.
一张受害人的照片传遍网络
A photo pops up of the vic.
里面刚好就有末影人
With Thinman photobombing.
这么说末影人会跟踪自己的目标
So Thinman stalking folks.
根据民间传说来说 是的
According to the lure.
蠢蛋传说还差不多
According to the idiots.
为什么我们不知道这些事情
How come none of these vics pinged our radar.
我确定 很多的迷之死亡案件
I'm pretty sure the mysterious death.
都跟非自然生物 不沾边
Can be chalked up to nonsupernatural causes.
因为 说实在的
That,and honestly.
大部分的照片都是做出来的
Most of these photos look pretty fake.
Cassy的死也是假的吗
Even Cassy's.
Cassy的死是真的
Except Cassy's.
Cassy的死亡照片不是做出来的
Cassy's photo wasn't doctored.
不论她后面那是什么
Whatever was behind her.
一定是真实存在的
Was really there.
我还是不明白
Okay,well that doesn't make any senses to me.
为什么它能既是真的又是假的
How could something be both real and fake at the same time.
那个女孩的死
The girl is dead.
一点儿都不假
And that's about as real as it gets.
好吧 那么
All right,so.
她死前做的最后一件事
The last thing she did was she took a.
是用手机自拍了一张照片
Photo on her phone.
那照片怎么传到网上去的
How did that photo end up online.
不知道
No clue.
那张图最初是发到一个末影人粉丝论坛上的
It was originally posted to a Thinman fan forum.
但是IP地址查不到
But the IP address was blocked.
等等 那玩意儿还有粉丝
Wait,wait,wait,this thing has fans.
好吧什么玩意儿都有粉丝
Of course it does.
一定是 有人想把照片发到网上
Then somebody wanted the photo on the internet.
鬼魂可没有这个本事
I'm guessing the ghost didn't hop online to post it.
探长在吗
Is the Sheriff around.
我们有几个问题要问
Couple of questions we'd like to ask.
很抱歉
Sorry to disappoint.
探长去打猎了
Sheriff's on a hunting trip.
但还是很感谢你们能来
But I appreciate you agents being here.
我会尽力帮助你们
You can use all the help I can get.
你们发现它的时候 它就是坏的吗
Wait a second,was it cracked when you found it.
有可能是她自己弄掉了
Maybe she dropped it.
求救电话是半夜11点59分挂断的
911 called went dead at 11:59.
那张照片是什么发的
What time was the photo posted.
凌晨2点左右
Around 2 am.
但法医说受害人是在午夜死的
But the corner had the death at midnight.
怎么会发照片
How could she had posted a photo on a phone.
根本不可能的事
That's impossible.
也可能是非自然案件
Or supernatural.
什么
What.
为什么这么说
Why would you say that.
有两个家伙来过
Couple of fellows came by.
问了有关这个女孩的事情
And asking questions about the girl's death.
说他们可能会帮上忙
Suggested they might be able to help.
他们还给我留了一本他们写的书
They gave me a book they wrote.
- 是关于 - 末影人吗
- About - Thinman.
没错
Yeah.
不是粉啊
Not a fan.
探员们
Agents.
你们能来真是太好了
Thanks for coming.
那两个蠢蛋在这儿干什么
What are those two crapshoots doing here.
我觉得让媒体来查查也无伤大雅
I figure it wouldn't hurt to go a little medium,you know.
之前距离2个郡以外 很多人都在
Two counties's over,folks were.
搜索
Combing the place for.
8月那个死去的小男孩儿
Poor little dead boy back in August.
警察说是变态作案
Cops said,psychic do the thing.
有时候就是头脑那么一冲动
Just bang boom.
第二天就多了一具尸体
Got a body a day later.
抱歉
Excuse me.
有没有监控录像带
Is there any security camera footage.
有的 跟我来
Oh,yeah,just.
嘿
Hey.
我是不是警告过你们别再出现了
Thought I told you to beat it.
怎么 你想干什么
Oh,what are you gonna do.
想把我们赶跑吗
You gonna out me.
探员先生
Agent.
在犯罪现场搞小道消息
Okay,come on,playing paparazzi in a crime scnene.
你们到底有什么底气
Who is that help with yourselves.
博客圈 Dean
The bloggers,Dean.
我们有追随者
The believers.
只需要一点证据 就能证明
Everyone who needs just a little proof to know that.
末影人确实存在
Thinman is out there.
这么说网上有很多人
So you say there's a lot of folks online.
都是死忠粉吗
That are pretty die hard about this thing.
没错
Oh,yeah.
你们把某些西藏符号放在一起
You throw the right Tibetan symbol into the mix.
就没想过会让末影人变成
You dumpasses ever think the Thinman comes to life.
冥想体吗
As a Tulpa.
成千上万的人可以
Because thousands of people.
冥想出一个一模一样的末影人吗
Can agree that Thinman is any one thing.
每篇博客里的故事都不一样
The lore changes blog to blog.
他不是冥想体
He's not a Tulpa.
好吧 好吧
Okay,alright,alright.
现在
Right here,right now.
废话少说
Cut the crap.
你们究竟知不知道
Do either of you actually know.
末影人到底是什么东西
What Thinman is.
不知道
No.
我们只是在电视录像演超自然学专家
We just play supernaturalist on tv.
我们完全不知道自己到底在干什么
We have no idea what we're doing.
我们当然知道
Of course we do.
末影人是半人 半树
Thinman is part man,part tree.
有人说他来自于
Some people believe that.
孤僻男孩儿最大的噩梦
He emerged from the nightmare of a autistic boy.
了解 你们俩什么都不知道
All right,you have no idea.
快过来看这个
Fellas,you want to see this.
注意看
All rihgt,check it out.
他是怎么从停车场瞬间到达餐馆里的
Alright,so,how did he jump from the parking lot.
餐馆的门上锁了吗
To the dinner.The doors were locked.
录像带显示 Troy10分钟前刚锁上门
The footage shows Trey locked it ten minutes before.
锁 还是没锁 都无关紧要
Locked,not locked,it doesn't matter.
所有人都知道末影人会瞬移
Everyone knows Thinman can teleport.
我的EMF都没动静
I didn't even get a blip on my EMF.
也许根本就不是个鬼魂
So maybe it's not a ghost.
你们现在相信了吗
You feds believers now.
好吧 我们该走了
Okay,we gonna go.
加油啊 副警长 探员们
Good work,deputy,agent.
快走 Ed
Let's go,Ed.
- 能再看看吗 - 可以
- See it again? - Okay.
我的天啊
Holy wow.
有人把餐馆里有关末影人的视频
Someone posted the dinner footage of Thinman.
发到了我们博客的评论区
In comments section of our blog.
谁发的
Who.
管他谁发的
Who cares.
保持这个车速
Maintain current velocity.
Harry 你为什么
Harry,why.
为什么要换上忍者夜行衣
Why are you putting your ninja outfit on.
我不会坐以待毙看着其他人去死
I'm not gonna wait for someone else to die.
我要找到末影人 就在今晚
I'm gonna find Thinman tonight.
去哪儿找
Where.
森林啊
The woods.
多明显
Obvi.
不 一点儿都不
It's kind of general.
民间传说记载
Well the lore says that.
末影人在树木周围出没
Thinman hangs out by trees and.
森林不就是有一堆树木出没的地方吗
And the woods were trees hang out.
做掉一个镇子
To kill in town.
埋伏在附近的森林再方便不过了
Local woods is the best bet.
已经有两个人死了
Two people are dead.
是真的死了
Really dead.
我一直都在想
And I just keep thinking that you know.
也许该让Sam和Dean插手就对了
Maybe Sam and Dean should just take over.
首先
First of all.
绝不
Hell no.
别在我的彩虹上下雨了
And quit raining on my rainbow.
不下雨是不可能有彩虹的
Rainbows can't happen without rain.
别跟我谈科学
Don't try to use science with me.
这是 感情上的事儿
This is about...about a feeling.
我们不能在找到末影人的
We can't quit when we're so close to.
关键时刻放弃 我们付出的努力
Finding Thinman and finally making up for.
和心血马上就要收到回报了
Everything we've lost because of...what we do.
但是让专业人士来接管
Okay,it wouldn't be the worst idea though.
也不是最坏的注意
You know,if we leave it to the professionals.
我们就是专业的 Ed
We are the professionals,Ed.
你真的打算去森林吗
So the woods.
任何森林 Ed 任何一个
Any woods,Ed,any woods.
说一个不大靠谱的想法吧
Just grasping at straws here.
说到瞬间移动 我想到的是十字路口恶魔
When I think teleport,I think crossroads demon.
嗯 恶魔喜欢捅别人 还看youtube
Eh,demon likes to stab and watch youtube.
这又怎么了
Why not.
说到这个
By the way,speaking of which.
Triel被刺的视频
The video of Triel getting knifed.
网上已经有了
It's already online.
有2000多的关注度 就好像
Has like two thousands views.It's like.
有人想让大家看到末影人一样
Someone wants people to see Thinman in action.
因为大家都会看 社会越来越变态
Cause people will watch.'Cause people are sick.
什么时候热门视频从
And when did viral go from that.
大猩猩宝宝摔下树枝
Baby chimp falling out of a tree to.
变成嫌犯录影带了
Killer Candid camera.
你知道什么视频会火吗
You know what video would gone viral.
如果我们还留着的话
If we still had it.
你五岁的时候
When you are five.
穿成蝙蝠侠的样子
You got dressed up as batman.
从屋顶跳下去
And you jumped off the shed.
你以为你能飞起来
Cause you thought you could fly.
是你先跳的
After you jumped first.
是啊 我那时候九岁 扮的可是了超人
Yeah,I was nine and I was dressed up like superman,okay.
所有人都知道蝙蝠侠不能飞
And everybody knows batman can't fly.
我不知道啊 就摔断了胳膊
I didn't know that and I broke my arm.
是啊没错
Oh yeah,you did.
然后我用推车把你从去了急诊室
Then I drove you to the ER on my handle bars.
美好时光啊
Good times.
是啊
Yeah,they were.
进来吧
Come on in.
我得告诉你们一件重要的事
I gotta tell you guys something important.
然后这案子就归你们管
And then the case is yours.
我是Harry 打鬼特工队个人行动
Harry here,solo ghostfacer.
独自调查一处疑似末影人的藏身之处
Investigate a possible Thinman habitat.
在森林深处
In the woods.
独自一人 探寻森林深处
All alone,deep in the woods.
一个人要知道自己即将面对
A man could lose him marbles.
未知的恐怖时一定会吓疯
Being so close to the blade of doom.
幸运的是
Lucky for us.
我们玩儿的就是疯
I'm really good at marbles.
不管你们怎么看待打鬼特工队
All right,either you bleed Ghostfacers red.
我还是要告诉你们
Or you don't.
Spruce想要离开去成立一个小公司
If Spruce wanted to start a startup.
Maggie一心扎进了场地轮滑
Maggie's heart was in the roller derby.
我没有理由阻止他们
Who am I gonna stop them.
但是Harry 我不能让他被那女的看不起
But Harry,I couldn't let him give into his girl.
她说打鬼特工队蠢
I mean,she called ghostfacers stupid.
她说我们蠢
Stupid.
你们相信吗
Can you believe that.
她爸爸手里的基金值多少钱我不在乎
I don't care how much money her daddy's hedge fund has.
但我不能眼睁睁看着Harry
I just couldn't watch Harry become a.
变得任人摆布
Corporate stooge.
目前为止你说的都是个人恩怨情感纠纷
Okay,this all sounds like sad times at Bitchmont High.
这些跟这个案子有什么关系
What does this have to do with the case.
Harry那时候要走 所以我需要
Harry was gonna leave so I needed to.
给他一个留下的理由
Give him a reason to stay.
末影人是我编出来的
I...I made up Thinman.
末影人跟踪被害人
Thinman stalks his victims.
但是现在情况恰恰相反 亲爱的朋友们
But the tables have turned,my friends.
跟踪别人的 现在正被人跟踪着
The stalker is now the stalkee.
你是说 这堆故事真的是扯淡
So you are saying this crap is actually crap.
一张管家的老照片
One old photo of a butler.
很多的后期制作
A lot of photoshop later and I.
然后匿名发到一个恐怖论坛上
Posted it on one of those horror forum under anonymous.
然后就火了
And it blew up.
是 我只做了一个假案子
Yeah,I only faked one case for us.
我们都快回家的时候
And then we're packing up to go home.
有个人发了一个末影人的网址 然后
When somebody posted a sighting of Thinman so.
我们就去看了 然后
We went after it,that's how a Thinman.
末影人就变成人人皆知的传说了
Became a crowdsourced legend.
我们怎么 我们可是前锋
How could...We were at the front of it.
整件事都有一种真实感
It felt like something.It.
被人追捧着的感觉真是太棒了
It was so awesome to have a following.
Harry 他只是
And Harry,he's just.
太投入了
He's so into it.
Ed 你必须告诉他
Ed,you have to tell him.
你不理解
You don't get it.
我们就是为了末影人而存在的
We were the Thinman guys.
没有了末影人 我们只是
Without the Thinman,we're just.
普通人
Guys,just.
满口空谈的妄想家
We're just puffs.
- 什么 - 什么
- What - What.
如果我告诉Harry 他会离开打鬼特工队的
If I tell Harry,he's gonna leave the ghostfacers.
如果你不告诉他 他一样会离开
Listen,if you don't tell him,he is gonna leave anyway.
相信我
Trust me here.
秘密会毁坏任何一种关系
Secrets ruin relationships.
好吧 时机成熟我就告诉他
Okay,I'll just tell him when the time's right.
你最好现在就告诉他
Time's right now,Chief.
那个 他啊
Well,he's.
他不在这儿
He's not here.
他去林子里找末影人了
He's out in the woods searching for Thinman.
好吧 这个末影人
Okay,because this Thinman.
或者别的什么玩意儿
Or whatever this hell this thing is.
已经杀了两个人了
Has killed two people.
现在Harry又一个人在林子里
And now Harry is in the woods alone.
也就是几棵树而已
Well,actually it's more like wood.
我把他送到便利店
'Cause I dropped him off by some trees.
后面的树旁边
Behind the grocery store.
别急啊 没事的
Guys,come on,he is gonna be fine.
喂
Guys.
我们现在看到的是
All right,what we have here is.
看似树枝状的东西
It looks like a formation of sticks.
堆成堆
In shape of a pile.
有可能是末影人留给我们的哦
Could've been left here for us by Thinman.
那是什么
What's that.
我天
Oh,oh my god.
Oh my god.
我天
周围还有别人
We are not alone.
太紧了吗
Too tight.
不
Nope.
我感觉挺好 挺好
I'm good,I'm good.
- 是吗 - 等回去的时候
- Yeah? - I think I'm just gonna have to.
钉住就好
Staple it when we get back to the motal.
我们是对的 Ed 末影人是真的
We were right,Ed!Thinman is real.
是吗
Yeah.
在那边发现了几条刚压过的车胎痕迹
Some fresh tire tracks back over there.
我照了几张相
I took some photos.
为什么
What for.
因为车主就是捅了你一刀的人
Because that car might belong to whoever knifed you.
给了我一刀的是末影人
Whoever cut me was Thinman.
末影人不开车
And Thinman doesn't drive.
就是末影人干的 混蛋
It was Thinman,jackass.
我真不该就这么告诉你们
I shouldn't have to connect the dots for you guys.
我以为你们都是聪明人 也许是
I figured,you know,you're both intelegent-maybe.
呃 Harry
Um,Harry.
怎么
What.
你为什么不早告诉我
Why didn't you tell me that before.
因为我 我觉得
Because I don't know,I thought.
我害怕你会生气
You're gonna get mad.
猜得不错 Ed 我是很生气
Oh,good guess,Ed.I'm mad.
对你非常 非常生气
I'm really,really mad at you right now.
我能看得出来
I can see that.
你毁了我人生中的一部分
You crashed the Jenga Tower of our lives.
我本来是要结婚的
I was gonna get married.
我抛弃了她
I left her.
跟你生活在谎言里
To run around with you living in some lies.
至少我们度过了一段美好的时光
At least we're living it togerther.
你是认真的吗
Seriously.
你没开玩笑吧
如果我没造出末影人的谎言
If I hadn't struck gold with Thinman.
你现在就应该做一份无聊的工作
You'd be doing a boring job.
跟无聊的数字
Doing boring numbers.
每天还要给Dana的爸爸汇报
And answering to Dana's dad.
你明不明白 我拯救了你
Okay,I saved you,buddy.
把我从什么里拯救出来
Save me from what.
从美好的生活里
From living a nice life.
还是防止我被人捅上一刀
From not getting me stabbed.
你真是太自私了
How selfish can you be.
也许现在还不算太晚
Maybe it's not too late,you know.
你可以给她打个电话
You could call her and see.
没可能了
That's not gonna work.
也许 还有希望
Maybe...maybe it will.
不 不会的 想知道为什么吗
No,it's not,you want to know why.
因为她的肩上搭着另一个男人的手臂
Cause she's got some guy's arm wrapped around her neck.
她的状态也变得复杂了
And it's complicated,okay.
听着 Harry 从一开始 我们也不知道
Look,Harry,we didn't know from the start.
末影人到底是不是真的
If Thinman was real or not.
好吧
Okay.
我承认我隐瞒了部分情报
Maybe I had some inside knowledge.
但是如果我们一直为粉丝演下去
But does it really make a different.
真相是什么 还重要吗
If we keep it going for the fans.
他们永远都不会知道
They'll never know.
但我知道
I'll know.
你把我骗的团团转
You made a chump out of me,Ed.
嘿 我们能渡过这一关的
Harry,we can get throught this.
我们只要除掉末影人
We just debunk Thinman.
然后继续我们的打鬼特工队
And then we go back to Ghostfacers.
我做不到
I can't.
我无法再相信你了 Ed
I can't trust you anymore,Ed.
不要这样 Harry
Oh come on Harry.
我懂了 你是生气了
I get it,you're pissed,okay.
你说的这些都是气话
And you don't mean what you say.
Harry 告诉我你想怎么做
But Harry,just tell me what you need.
我去买杯咖啡
I'll go get some coffee and.
你在这儿坐着缓缓
You can stay here and chill.
嘿 怎么样了
Hey,how did it go.
嗯 呃
It went...um.
嘿
Hey.
你还好吗
You okay.
刚被现实狠狠打了一拳
I just got a punch right in the feels.
那些没有一个是真的 Sam
None of them was real,Sam.
Ed一直在装
Ed was just pretending.
现在他还要我一起装
And now he wants me to pretend.
装作这件事就可以过去了
Like this is something I could get past.
我明白你的意思
I know what you mean.
有些事情是你可以原谅的
Look there are things you can forgive.
有些不能
And there are things you can't.
那这件事呢
So which one is this.
这件事要看你自己怎么想了
That's something you got to figure out for yourself.
嘿
Hey.
我从轮胎痕迹上发现了一条线索 你要不要
I got a bead on those tire treads,if you want to.
怎么了
What's up.
这种车胎只给一种车用
So the tires were only made for one kind of car.
1989年的Geo Metro
The 1989 Geo Metro.
这个小镇 只有唯一一辆有注册
Town this small… There's only one registered here.
副警长说那是Roger的
And Deputy says it belongs to a guy named Roger.
他晚上在山下小镇的
Who works night security down at the hill.
北边当保安
On the north side of town.
这个会心灵传输的家伙 有工作还有车
So this thing teleported but it has a job and a car.
我们到底在对付什么
What are we dealing with.
走吧去查清楚
Let's go find out.
Sam和Dean有了新的线索
Sam and Dean caught something.
现在去收拾你的烂摊子
So...they are gonna clean up your mess.
你说得对 是我的烂摊子
You're right,it is my mess.
所以我才是应该去清理的人
I should be the one out there cleaning it up.
你只会让情况更糟
You'd just make it worse.
怎么
Oh what.
你以前离开Sam和Dean的时候都没意见
You were fine leaving Sam and Dean before.
现在是什么意思
Why not now.
我不想再当水母那样的软骨头了Harry
I don't want be a jellyfish spine anymore Harry.
水母没有骨头
Jellyfish don't have spines.
我就是这个意思
Exactly.
在遇到麻烦之前 在那些骗人的把戏之前
Before the heartache,before the lies.
我们说好了要帮助人的
We set out to help people,right.
是啊
Yeah.
大致是这样
Mostly.
所以我们为什么不挺身而出
And there is no reason not to get out there.
做我们说好要做的事呢
And do what we mostly set out to do.
Harry我可以让我们一切恢复正常
Harry,I can make it right for the both of us.
我们可以让一切恢复正常
We can make it right.
你的意思是
You...you mean.
你要和我一起吗
You want to come with me.
我不是说过 我和我搭档
I thought we said that my partner and I.
会处理好这件事的
Will take care of this.
听着哥们 我上司跑了
Look guys,my boss is AWOL.
我们也没有搜查证
We don't have a warrant.
如果这事儿搞砸了
My ass is on the line.
我肯定完蛋
If this thing goes to the sideways.
好吧你就 靠后站
All right just...stay back.
一直想试试这玩意儿来着
Always wanted to use these things.
所以你是末影人是吧
So you're Thinman.
如果你不是一副吃翔吃太多的样子
That would make sense if it didn't.
确实还挺可信的
Look like you just ate a fat camp.
天呐Sam 快让他闭嘴
Oh god,Sam make him stop.
好吧到底是怎么回事 你到底是谁 Norwood
Hey,so what's the deal?What are you,Norwood.
你是恶魔吗
You a demon.
你在餐馆是怎么瞬间移动的
I mean how did you teleport back at the diner.
团队合作
Team effort.
所以压根就没有什么瞬间移动
So there was no teleporting.
就是两个傻叉重演惊声尖叫
Just a couple of douche bags doing a scream thing.
等下 我认识你
Wait,I know who you are.
你是小餐馆的打工仔
You are the busboy from the diner.
你就是看你老板不爽杀他的吗
So,what,you just wanted to kill your boss.
Trey是个混蛋
Trey was a dick.
那Cassy呢
And what about Cassy.
她又做了什么
What did she do.
她不愿意跟我约会
She wouldn't go out with me.
所以我就把她介绍给别人了
So I set her up with someone else.
我的刀
My knife.
你太逗了
Good one,Rog.
看来警长也没能出城
I see the sherrif didn't make it out of town.
他当时要是给我准假就没事了
He really should've given me the time off I asked for.
所以你就杀了他
So you killed him.
我谁也没杀
I didn't kill anyone.
都是Roger杀的
Roger did.
他是个小疯子
He is a psycho.
我是个空想家
I'm the visionary.
我不怪你们看低我
I don't blame you for underestimating me.
每个人都是这样
Everbody does.
光鲜的联邦探员
Fancy fed.
从来这儿的那一刻起
Come in here and treating me like.
就把我当猴儿耍
A paper monkey from the get-go.
不过我才是末影人
But I was Thinman the whole time.
你知道那种感觉有多爽吗
Do you have any idea how good that felt.
不 变态 我体会不到
No sicko,I can't say that I do.
长得这么俊怎么会知道
Yeah pretty boy doesn't know.
被人忽视是什么感觉
What it's like to feel invisible.
在一个300人的小镇里 长大
To grow up in a town of 300 people.
但从没有人看你一眼又是什么感觉
And nobody sees you.
他们根本不会注意我们
They didn't see us.
所以 你们是怎么认识的
So How did you two meet.
互撸网吗
Wackjob.com.
不是
No.
我们只是在一个没人的酒吧里随便聊了两句
Just a couple of schmoes in an empty bar.
一见如故 没想到我和Roge
We hit it off,turns out me and Roge.
我们都是阴谋论的终极爱好者
We are both total conspiracy-theory junkies.
之后我们就发现了末影人 然后 砰
And then we found Thinman,and,bam.
我们攻击了许多留言版块
We blew up all over the message boards.
那你们现在是在做什么
So what is this then.
变态角色扮演吗
Some sort of a twisted cosplay.
是真人扮演
Cos-real.
博客是挺有意思的 但是
You know,blogging was fun but.
让我猜猜 但是你们还想得寸进尺
But,let me guess,you wanted something more.
要知道 你们干的这些混账事情
You realize what you two jackasses are doing.
并没让你们变成末影人
Doesn't make you Thinman.
你们只是两个冒牌货
That makes you copycat killers.
我就是末影人
That makes me Thinman.
你不会跟别人说我不是的
You are not telling anyone I'm not.
因为死人是不会说话的
Cause you'll be too dead to talk.
好戏开始
Show time.
你们两个真走运
You two are lucky ducks.
有机会在我们最好的视频里做主角
You're the stars of our best video yet.
这段视频会传遍天下
I want it goes viral.
大家都会知道末影人是真的
Everyon will know Thinman is real.
好了 开拍
And action.
不不 不要
No no,don't.
Harry
Harry.
他在我这儿
He got me.
他抓到我了
He got me back.
大坏蛋要哭鼻子了 蠢蛋
It's scooby-doo time,doushbag.
把你的面具拿下来
Take off the mask.
我知道你不是末影人
I know you are not Thinman.
你就是个冒片卑货
You are just a me-me.
念冒牌货
And it prononces me.
但是写成片卑啊
It spells m e m e,though.
那是一个字
Then the second is silent.
你是个冒片卑货 冒片货
You are a meme...a man meme.
你是我创造出来的
And I invented you.
多谢赐教
Good to know.
我喜欢那些经典的著作 Ed
I'm a lover of the classics,Ed.
我们现在面对的
Then what we have here.
是一个典型的Frankenstein局面
Is a "Frankenstein" situation.
我的意思是 哇靠
I mean WOW.
我们的创造者
The creator.
我们本来想
I mean we were gonna.
让你们中一个活着给我们讲故事
Let one of you guys live to tell us the story.
不过现在
But now.
等你们俩一死
Once you two are dead.
就没有人能证明末影人只是你们想象出来的了
There will be no proof that Thinman was your brainchild.
等等 不不不
Wait!No no no.
听我说
Look,look at me.
这全都是我的错
This is all my fault,okay.
都是我的错
It's all my fault.
我的子弹够杀你们俩了
I got enough bullets for both of you.
这事儿算是解决了
So we are good in there.
是啊
Yeah.
有了末影人录影带 再加上我布置过的现场
With the Thinman footage and the way I set the bodies.
应该有足够的证据可以指出
Should be enough breadcrumbs to make it look like.
是那两个神经病解决了对方
Those two psychos offed each other.
他们只是普通人
They were just people,man.
他们不是恶魔也不是怪物
They weren't demons,they weren't monsters.
只是人类而已
Just fricking people.
我说过了 人类都不正常了
Well like I said,people are sick.
我们和好了吗
So,are we cool.
我觉得我们永远都不会好了
I don't think we ever will be.
我们把事情解决了
You know we made it right.
我们打赢了他们
We beat the guys.
我们可以试着重新开始
This will be our shot to start the old.
打鬼特工队的旅程
Ghostfacers again.
我只是来和你一起解决末影人的事情
I came here with you to finish this thing with Thinman.
这不仅仅是一个章节的完结 Ed
I wasn't just...closing a chapter,Ed.
是一整本书
It was the whole dang book.
你刚刚救了我的命
You saved my life back there.
我杀了一个人 Ed
I killed a guy,Ed.
那是个坏人Harry
He was a bad guy,Harry.
那是一条人命 Ed
He was a guy,Ed.
就因为你那破玩意太多人死掉了
Too many people have died cause of your crap.
我做这些是为了我们两个人
I've done all this crap for us.
我不明白你怎么就是不懂呢
And I don't know why you don't see that.
不 不是的
No,no.
你做那些只是为了你自己
You did this for you.
我已经够宽容了
There's a lot things I can forgive.
但是这件事我无法释怀
But this isn't one of them.
那我们两个之间是怎样
So what does this mean about us.
我们之间
It means.
一言难尽
It's complicated.
我可以搭个顺风车吗
Can I get a ride from you guys.
可以 当然
Yeah sure.
Harry 你还好吗
Harry,you okay.
我还好
Yeah.
好吧 不怎么好
I mean...no.
你跟一个人在一起那么多年
You roll with a guy so many years you start to think.
你相信他永远都会守在你身边
He's always gonna be next to you.
哪怕年华渐逝 只能凭栏望景
Like when you're old and you're drinking on the porch.
还有一个人能与你相濡以沫
He'll be in that nother rocking chair.
直到世事更迭你才发现
And something happens and you realize.
相濡以沫 不如相忘于江湖
That other chair's gone,empty.
我想你能明白我的意思
You know what I mean